Finding aid to Office of the President William Allan Neilson files CA.MS.00013
Smith College Archives
- Series III. Subjects
  - Neilson Chair of Research- general, undated (Box 416, Folder 15)
  - Neilson Chair of Research, 1927-39 (Box 416, Folder 16)
  - Political Issues, 1921-32 (Box 416, Folder 17)
  - Post Office, 1921-32 (Box 416, Folder 18)
  - Prizes- general, 1925-39 (Box 416, Folder 19)
  - Prizes- Misc. A-Z, 1920-39 (Box 416, Folder 20)
  - Prizes- Babcock, Elizabeth Poetry Prize, 1938-39 (Box 416, Folder 21)
  - Prizes- Brigham, Margaret Wimple Prize, 1932 (Box 416, Folder 22)
  - Prizes- Butrick, James Gardner Prize, 1927 (Box 416, Folder 23)
  - Prizes- Foote, Henry Lewis Memorial Prize, 1923-27 (Box 416, Folder 24)
  - Prizes- French, Clara Prize, 1922-29 (Box 416, Folder 25)
  - Prizes- Jordan, Mary Augusta Prize, 1922-30 (Box 416, Folder 26)
  - Prizes- Saul, E. Adele Scott Prize, 1921-24 (Box 416, Folder 27)
  - Prizes- van Kleek, Mary Prize, 1918-29 (Box 416, Folder 28)
  - Publications (College) Seelye, L.C. "the Early History of Smith College"(1923) Correspondence, 1923-29 (Box 416, Folder 29)
  - Publications (College) Wilder "the Early Years of a Zooligist"(1930) Correspondence, 1930-31 (Box 416, Folder 30)
  - Publications (College) Misc., 1923-38 (Box 416, Folder 31)
  - Publicity-Correspondence, 1920-40; undated (Box 416, Folder 32)
  - Publicity- Press Releases, 1929-40 (Box 416, Folder 33)
  - Question Box, 1924-27; undated (Box 416, Folder 34)
  - Radio, 1923-40 (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - Religion, 1925-31 (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Seal (College), 1921-37 (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Scandal, 1921 (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships- General, 1918-39 (Box 417, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships- Misc. A-Z, 1919-38 (Box 417, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships-Hamm, Arthur Ellis Memorial Scholarship- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships- Latin American, 1925 (Box 417, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships- Presser Foundation Scholarship- Correspondence, 1922-39 (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships- Veltin Association Scholarship- Corresponence, 1926 (Box 417, Folder 10)
  - Security, 1921-31 (Box 417, Folder 11)
  - Skits, Songs etc, undated (Box 417, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Sophia and Family, 1922-32 (Box 417, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Sophia Homestead, 1935; undated (Box 417, Folder 14)
  - Smoking, 1922-35 (Box 417, Folder 15)
  - Social Life, 1919-39 (Box 417, Folder 16)
  - Statistics, 1918-33 (Box 417, Folder 17-18)
  - Taxes, 1919-38 (Box 417, Folder 19)
  - Teacher's Oath Bill, 1935-39 (Box 417, Folder 20)
  - Train Service-Correspondence, 1917-34 (Box 417, Folder 21)
  - Unions, 1918-36 (Box 417, Folder 22)
  - Vespers, 1918-46 (Box 417, Folder 23)
  - War Work, 1917-21; undated (Box 417, Folder 24-26)
  - Water Power, 1919-20 (Box 417, Folder 27)
- Series IV. Confidential
  - Art Museum Expenditures, 1915-32; undated (Box 429, Folder 1-3)
- SERIES V. Publications
  - Books: 15 volumes (417.1)
  - Books: 10 volumes (471.2)